let questionListOne = [
    {
        question: "What is the name of Ross and Monica's dog when they were kids?",
        answers: ['Buster', 'Fluffy', 'Rex', 'Rover'],
        correctAnswer: 'Buster'
    },
    {
        question: "Which character famously yelled, 'We were on a break!' during the series?",
        answers: ['Ross', 'Chandler', 'Joey', 'Phoebe'],
        correctAnswer: 'Ross'
    },
    {
        question: "What is the name of the coffee shop where the friends frequently hang out?",
        answers: ['Central Perk', 'Java Jolt', 'Espresso Emporium', 'The Percolator'],
        correctAnswer: 'Central Perk'
    },
    {
        question: "Who played the role of Ross Geller in the TV show 'Friends'?",
        answers: ['Matt LeBlanc', 'Matthew Perry', 'David Schwimmer', 'Courteney Cox'],
        correctAnswer: 'David Schwimmer'
    },
    {
        question: "What is the profession of Ross Geller in the show?",
        answers: ['Paleontologist', 'Chef', 'Actor', 'Accountant'],
        correctAnswer: 'Paleontologist'
    },
];

let questionListTwo = [
    {
        question: "Which character briefly lived with a woman named Janice, known for her distinctive laugh?",
        answers: ['Monica', 'Chandler', 'Phoebe', 'Joey'],
        correctAnswer: 'Chandler'
    },
    {
        question: "Which character is known for her famous song, 'Smelly Cat'?",
        answers: ['Monica', 'Phoebe', 'Rachel', 'Janice'],
        correctAnswer: 'Phoebe'
    },
    {
        question: "What is the name of Ross and Monica's father?",
        answers: ['Bob', 'Jack', 'Richard', 'George'],
        correctAnswer: 'Jack'
    },
    {
        question: "What does Joey not share?",
        answers: ['His apartment', 'His food', 'His clothes', 'His acting tips'],
        correctAnswer: 'His food'
    },
    {
        question: "What is the name of the coffee shop employee who frequently serves the friends at Central Perk?",
        answers: ['Gunther', 'Walter', 'Roger', 'Steven'],
        correctAnswer: 'Gunther'
    },
];

let questionListThree = [
    {
        question: "What is Joey's catchphrase?",
        answers: ['How you doin\'?', 'What\'s up?', 'Hey there!', 'Greetings!'],
        correctAnswer: 'How you doin\'?'
    },
    {
        question: "What is the profession of Chandler Bing?",
        answers: ['Actor', 'Chef', 'Accountant', 'Advertising Executive'],
        correctAnswer: 'Advertising Executive'
    },
    {
        question: "Which character accidentally threw a woman's wooden leg into a fire?",
        answers: ['Ross', 'Joey', 'Chandler', 'Monica'],
        correctAnswer: 'Joey'
    },
    {
        question: "What is the name of Ross's second wife?",
        answers: ['Emily', 'Janice', 'Carol', 'Susan'],
        correctAnswer: 'Emily'
    },
    {
        question: "What game did the friends play to decide who would have to move out of Monica's apartment?",
        answers: ['Rock, Paper, Scissors', 'Flip the Coin', 'Spin the Bottle', 'Russian Roulette'],
        correctAnswer: 'Rock, Paper, Scissors'
    },
]

export default {
    questionListOne, questionListTwo, questionListThree
}